diplomaplus.net 2009-06-12

# Commonwealth Corporation: Privacy Policy

Home: About Us: Privacy Policy

| President's Welcome  |    
---|---  
Mission  |    
Board of Directors |    
Management Committee |    
In the News |    
Careers |    

Privacy Policy 

Commonwealth Corporation does not automatically collect any personal identifying information about you when you visit our site. This site may collect voluntary information from you through email that you send through the web site. An email sent by you to this site will contain personal identifying information.

We use the term "personal identifying information" to mean any information that could reasonably be used to identify you, including your name, address, e-mail address, Social Security number, birth date, bank account information, credit card information, or any combination of information that could be used to identify you.

**E-mail Containing Personal Information** : If you decide to send us personal identifying information, such as a mailing address for the purpose of receiving further information on a program or service, the personal information received is used solely for responding to your requests. We may also forward your email to other employees within the Corporation who may be better able to assist you. With respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information, Commonwealth Corporation makes every effort to ensure compliance with the Public Records Law, the Fair Information Practices Act (Massachusetts General Laws Chapter 66A), Executive Order 412, and other applicable laws and regulations.

Commonwealth Corporation **does not encrypt** incoming e-mail, therefore you should **not** send information that you consider highly sensitive (Social Security number, birth date, bank account information, credit card information) through this web site. We use standard security measures to ensure that your personally identifiable information is not lost, misused, altered, or unintentionally destroyed.

**Information Automatically Collected and Stored by this Site** Commonwealth Corporation does collect and store some information automatically in our database. When you visit our web site to read or download information, we collect and store the following:

  * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * Date and time you accessed our site
  * Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site
  * Your internet browser and operating system

We use this collected information to create summary statistics and to assess the frequency of visits to our site and the popularity of the various pages. This information allows us to make our site more useful for our viewers.

**Cookie Use Notice** Commonwealth Corporation uses "cookies" on a limited number of our web pages. These cookies allow us to provide better service to our viewers. Commonwealth Corporation does not use cookies to collect any personal identifying information from users or to track user activities beyond our web site. We do not maintain copies of cookies on our web site after you leave our web site.

Commonwealth Corporation uses only "session cookies". Session cookies are temporarily stored in your computer's memory. They are normally deleted from a user's computer when the user logs off the computer or exits the browser.

For security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, our web site also employs software programs to monitor network traffic in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

**Links to other sites outside Commonwealth Corporation:** Our Web site has many links to other web sites. When you link to any of these web sites, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. 

**Definitions** : **Cookies** are small pieces of temporary data that are exchanged between a web site and a user's computer which enable a "session", or "dialog", to be established between the two machines. A cookie file contains unique information that a web site can use to track such things as a password, a list of web pages you have visited, and the date when you looked at a specific web page, or to identify your session at a particular web site. 

A **session** establishes the selected information (IP Address, date and time, name of web page visited, browser and operating system information) and it is recorded in a database. The session is broken when the web server does not receive further requests from your computer or you simply exit your browser. 

An **Internet Protocol Address** ( **IP Address)** is a series of numbers that identifies each computer and machine connected to the Internet. An IP address enables a server on a computer network to send you the file that you have requested on the Internet. The IP address disclosed to us might identify the computer from which you are accessing the Internet, or a server owned by your Internet Service Provider. Because it is machine-specific, rather than person-specific, an IP address is not, in and of itself, personal identifying information.
